Oh, my God, I love this chicken.
Ce poulet est délicieux.
Oh, you know what they say, "The best things in life are free."
"Rien n'est meilleur que ce qui est gratuit", comme on dit.
You're right. I eat your food a lot. How about this?
OK, je mange beaucoup chez vous.
You can raid my fridge any time you want.
Fille mon frigo.
Oh, that's very kind of you.
C‘est très gentil.
Next time I have a hankering to wash down a D-cell battery...
Dès que j'aurai envie d‘une pile usagée
...with ajar of old pickle juice I'll come a-knocking.
au jus de cornichons, je me précipite.
Hey, Raj, you didn't send your RSVP in.
Ra], tu n'as pas répondu à l'invitation.
I'm supposed to ask you if you're bringing someone.
Est-ce que tu seras accompagné ?
I'll let you know.
Je te le dirai.
Could you make it soon? There's a battle over seating.
C‘est Battle Royale, ce plan de table.
In one corner, Bernadette's mom. In the other three, mine.
Dans un coin, la mère de Bernadette. Dans les trois autres, la mienne.
Yeah, I hate wedding receptions. lwish the bride and groom...
Je hais ces réceptions. Les mariés devraient
...would take a cue from Bilbo Baggins.
prendre exemple sur Bilbon.
Slip on the ring, disappear, and everyone goes home.
On passe l‘anneau, on disparaît et c‘est terminé.
Oh, you liked Professor Geyser's wedding.
Tu as aimé celui du Pr Geyser.
They had a make-your-own-sundae bar.
Il y avait un buffet à sundaes.
Do you know, on one trip, ljust had a bowl of nuts.
Lors d'un passage,je n'ai pris que des noix.
Anyway, you gotta let me know if you have a plus-one.
Si tu es accompagné, dis-le-moi.
If not, my mom's trying to sneak in the doctor...
Sinon, ma mére casera le médecin
...who sucked the fat out of her neck.
qui a fait sa lipo du cou.
All right, uh,fine.
Trés bien.
I'm coming and I'm bringing somebody.
Je serai accompagné.
Koothrappali plus one.
Koothrappali et un invité.
-Who are you bringing?
- Oui tu emmènes ? - Et toi ?
He's bringing me. Who are you bringing?
Moi. Qui tu emmènes ?
Wow, what a bunch of Nosey O'Donnells.
Tu te prends pour Rosie O'Concierge ?
Come on, who is it?
Allez, qui ?
I'm not telling. I'm from Asia. I'm mysterious. Deal with it.
Je suis asiatique et donc mystérieux. Faut vous y faire.
Howard, are you having a make-your-own-sundae bar?
Vous aurez un buffet à sundaes ?
Uh, I don't think so.
J'en doute.
Well, you should. Fifty percent of marriages end in divorce.
Tu devrais. 50 % des mariages se terminent en divorce,
But 10!) percent of make-your-own-sundae bars end in happiness.
alors que 100 % des bars à sundaes se terminent en bonheur.
-Hello, Mommy, Daddy. How are you? -Preny good, can'! complain.
- Maman, papa, comment ça va ? - Bien, on ne peut pas se plaindre.
Oh, I'm sure you can. Just give it a minute.
Je suis sûr que tu en es capable, ça va venir.
Listen, uh....
Écoutez,
There's something I want to talk to you about.
j'ai quelque chose a vous dire.
I wasn't ready until now...
Je n‘étais pas prêt,
...but I think it's time.
mais c‘est le moment.
It's ﬁnally happening.
Enﬁn.
You're coming out of the closet, aren't you?
Tu fais ton coming out ?
We love you and we accept your alternate lifestyle.
Nous !'aimons et acceptons ton choix.
Just keep it to yourself.
Mais ne le dis a personne.
No, I'm not gay.
Je ne suis pas gay.
If anything, I'm metrosexual.
Au pire, je suis métrosexuel.
What's that?
C‘est quoi ?
It means I like women as well as their skin-care products.
J'aime les femmes et leurs produits de beauté.
Well, if you're not coming out...
Si tu n‘es pas gay,
...why did you call us during the cricket semi-ﬁnals?
pourquoi appeler pendant la demi—ﬁnale du cricket ?
I think I'd like you to help me find a....
J'aimerais que vous m'aidiez a trouver...
A wife.
une femme.
And just to clarify, a female wife?
Pour être sûre : une femme, femme ?
Yes!
Oui!
Matchmaking. Very smart move, son.
Un mariage arrangé. Malin, mon ﬁls.
Much better than marrying for love.
Bien mieux que le mariage d‘amour.
We married for love.
On s‘est mariés par amour.
And it's been wonderful.
Et c‘est merveilleux.
Quantum physics makes me so happy.
La physique quantique me comble de joie.
Yeah? I'm glad.
Tant mieux.
It's like looking at the universe naked.
J'aime voir l‘univers nu.
-Hi. Guys got a minute? -Sure, what's up?
-Vous avez une minute ? -Oui.
l was thinking about Sheldon's little joke the other night...
J'ai repensé àla blague de Sheldon,
-...about me eating all your food. -Oh, that was no joke.
- sur la nourriture. - Je ne blaguais pas.
But I understand your confusion, as I am our group's resident cutup.
Je comprends ton erreur, je suis le larron de service.
I'm sorry, you are our resident cutup?
Pardon ? Notre larron de service ?
Yes.
Oui.
-Prove it. -Knock-knock.
- Prouve-le. - Toc-toc.
-Who's there? -lnterrupting physicist.
- Qui est la ? - Le physicien.
-lnterrupting phys-- -Muon. Ha, ha.
- Lequel ? - Muon !
Anyway, I got a little residual check from my commercial.
Bref, il me reste un chèque, de ma pub.
And I thought, "How about I get the guys a little thank-you to pay them back?"
Alors je me suis dit, comment remercier les garçons ?
So, Sheldon.... Ta-da.
Sheldon.…
A vintage, mint-in-box 1975 Mego Star Trek Transporter...
Un téléporteur Star Trek Vintage de 1975, dans son emballage,
...with real transporter action. Hot darn!
avec effet téléportation ! Trop bien !
-Where did you get that? -From Stuart at the comic-book store.
- Ça sort d'où ? - D‘une boutique de comics.
You went to the comic-book store by yourself?
Tu y es allée toute seule ?
Yeah. It was fun.
Oui, c‘était sympa.
I walked in and two different guys got asthma attacks.
En me voyant, deux mecs ont fait de l‘asthme.
Felt pretty good.
C‘est agréable.
Well, this calls for an expression of gratitude.
Ça nécessite un signe de gratitude.
Ooh, am I about to get a rare Sheldon Cooper hug?
Un rarissime câlin de Sheldon Cooper ?
No, not this time. Then they wouldn't be special.
Pas cette fois, ils sont spéciaux.
Click. Thanks, Penny.
Merci, Penny.
You're welcome.
De rien.
Don't worry, I didn't forget about you.
Je ne t'ai pas oublié.
Leonard, I got you a label-maker.
Leonard, voici une machine à étiqueter.
No, it's great.
Génial.
-Also, uh, mint-in-box. -Mm.
Dans son emballage.
-And I got you a Transporter too! -Awesome!
- Et un téléporteur. - Enorme !
Look, it was actually designed for my vintage Mr. Spock action figure.
Il a été conçu pour ma figurine Spock vintage.
Oh, that's great. Open it and put him in there.
Ouvre-Ie et mets—y Spock.
-Open it? -No, good Lord, no.
- L'ouvrir ? - Jamais.
Why? They're just toys.
C‘est un jouet.
-Collectibles. -They're mint-in-box.
- C‘est un collector. - Emballé.
Can't we open one up and take a look?
- On ne peut pas en ouvrir un ? - Non !
Once you open the box, it loses its value.
Une fois ouvert, ça ne vaut plus rien.
Yeah, yeah. My mom gave me the same lecture about my virginity.
C‘est ce que ma mère m‘a dit pour que je reste Vierge.
Gotta tell you, it was a lot more fun taking it out and playing with it.
Mais c‘est plus drôle de tout déballer pourjouer.
You sure you want us here when you meet this woman?
Tu es sûr que tu nous veux a ton rendez-vous ?
Oh, yes. In my culture, it's expected to have a chaperone to oversee a first date.
Ma culture exige qu'un chaperon assiste àla première rencontre.
I want to make a good impression. No offense, but with you here...
Je veux faire impression. Et a côté de vous,
...I look like I'm 6'2".
j'ai l‘air tellement grand.
The nuns always chaperoned the dances at my high school.
Au lycée, les bonnes sœurs surveillaient les bals.
They used to make us leave room between us for the Holy Spirit.
En dansant, on devait laisser de la place pour le Saint—Esprit.
Hindus do the same thing. Except they leave room for a cow. Ha, ha.
Les Hindous laissent de la place a une vache.
Listen, I love your charming racist humor.
Quel charmant humour raciste.
But any chance you could not mock my religion while she's here?
Ne te moque pas de ma religion devant elle.
-You made fun of me for eating lox. -Your people don't worship lox.
- Tu t'es moqué de mon saumon hier. - Vous ne vénérez pas le saumon.
Clearly you've never been to brunch with my cousins.
Tu n'as jamais déjeuné avec mes cousins.
So arranged marriages, the parents just decide...
Alors, les parents décident
...and then you get married?
et tu te maries ?
Oh, no, no. I get a say in it.
J'ai le choix. Mais je suis sûr que le leur sera plus sympa
...than the threesome I've been having with Aunt Jemima and Mrs. Butterworth.
que partager mes repas avec Tante Jemima et Mme Buttervvorth.
Excuse me, are you Rajesh?
Tu es Rajesh ?
Oh, yes. You must be Lakshmi.
Oui. Tu es Lakshmi ?
-Uh, nice to meet you. -Nice to meet you too.
- Enchanté. - Moi aussi.
-Hello. -Uh, and this is Howard.
- Bonsoir. - Et Howard.
HOWARD: Nice to meet you. -You too.
- Ravi. - Moi aussi.
Please, have a seat.
Assieds-toi.
[SINGSONG] I'm thinking double wedding.
Je pense a un double-mariage.
SPOCK: Dr. Cooper.
Dr Cooper.
ls someone there?
Il y a quelqu'un ?
Down here. On your desk.
Sur votre bureau.
-Spock? -I need to speak with you.
- Spock ? - Ecoutez-moi.
Fascinating.
Fascinant.
The only logical explanation is that this is a dream.
Seule explication logique : c‘est un rêve.
It is not the only logical explanation.
Ce n‘est pas la seule explication.
For example, you could be hallucinating...
Vous pourriez aussi délirer,
...after being hit on the head by, say, a coconut.
après qu‘une noix de coco vous est tombée sur la tête.
Was I hit on the head by a coconut?
Est-ce le cas ?
lam not going to dignify that with a response.
Je ne répondrai même pas.
Now to the matter at hand.
Venons-en au fait.
You need to play with the Transporter toy.
Vous devez jouer avec le téléporteur.
-But it's mint-in-box. -Yes.
- Mais il est emballé. - Bien entendu.
And to open it would destroy its value.
L 'ouvrir détruirait sa valeur.
But remember, like me...
Mais rappelez-vous : comme moi,
...you also have a human half.
vous êtes semi—humain.
Well, I'm not going to dignify that with a response.
Je ne répondrai même pas.
Consider this.
Réﬂéchissez.
-What is the purpose of a toy? -To be played with.
- A quoi sert un jouet ? - Ajouer.
Therefore, to not play with it would be...?
Ne pas jouer avec un jouet serait...
lllogical. Oh, damn it, Spock, you're right.
lllogique. Bon sang, Spock, vous avez raison.
I'll do it.
Je vais le faire.
Sheldon, wait.
Sheldon, attendez.
You have to wake up ﬁrst.
Réveillez-vous, d‘abord.
Oh, of course.
Bien sûr.
Set phasers to "Dumb," right? Ha, ha.
Phaseurs réglés sur “bête", pas vrai ?
Goodie, goodie, goodie.
Bien, bien, bien.
This is wrong, this is wrong. I'm so excited, but this is wrong.
C‘est mai. Trés mal. J'ai hâte, mais c‘est mal.
I'm gonna do it.
Je vais le faire.
I'm doing it.
Je le fais.
Idid it.
Je l'ai fait.
That's what I always thought 1975 smelled like.
L‘odeur de 1975, je le savais.
"One to beam down, Mr. Scott."
”Téléportation, M. Scott."
"Aye, aye, Mr. Spock."
”Bien, M. Spock."
Energize.
Générateur !
Don't be broken.
Ne sois pas cassé.
What did you make me do?
Que m‘avez-vous fait faire ?
Okay, okay. Think.
OK, réfléchis.
It's only logical.
C‘est logique.
My goodness, that was delicious.
C‘était succulent.
Well, I hope you saved room for chocolate lava cake.
J'espère qu'il te reste de la place pour le coulant au chocolat.
Impressive.
lmpressionnant.
What goes into making something like that?
Comment les fais-tu ?
Well, you start out by trying to make chocolate soufflé.
En essayant de faire un soufflé au chocolat.
And when it falls, you panic...
Quand il retombe, tu paniques
...quickly change the name, and voila, lava cake.
changes le nom, et voilà. Coulant.
I bet our parents are dying to know how things are going here.
Nos parents doivent se ronger les sangs.
Well, let's see.
Voyons.
Yep, three missed calls.
Trois appels manqués.
Four missed calls, two text messages, and a failed video chat.
Quatre appels, deux sms, et une vidéoconférence.
-I win. -Ha, ha.
J'ai gagné.
So, what are we going to tell them?
Qu'allons-nous leur dire ?
-l'd like to tell them things are going well. -Me too.
- Que ça va bien, j‘espère. - Je suis d‘accord.
But before we get their hopes up...
Avant qu‘ils ne s'emballent,
...we should probably make sure we're on the same page.
vérifions qu'on est sur la même longueur d‘onde.
What page are you on?
Sur quelle longueur es-tu ?
I'm on the one where I'm under a lot of pressure from my parents...
Celle où je subis une pression monstre de mes parents
...to get married and settle down and have a family.
pour me marier et fonder une famille.
And I'm going to do it so they don't find out I'm gay.
Je le fais pour leur cacher mon lesbianisme.
Say again.
Pardon ?
I'm gay.
Je suis lesbienne.
Like....
Comme...
Dude-on-dude, but with women?
deux mecs ensemble, mais en fille ?
I know a fake marriage isn't an honest way to live...
Un mariage bidon, c‘est malhonnête,
...but you, of all people, should know how difficult it is to come out.
mais tu sais, toi aussi, que c‘est dur de s'assumer.
Why me "of all people"?
”Moi aussi" ?
Well, there's a rumor back in New Delhi that you're--
Une rumeur court, à New Dehli, que…
How shall we say?
Comment dire…
--comfortable in a sari.
Que tu pourrais porter un sari.
-l'm not gay. -Really?
- Je ne suis pas gay. - Vraiment ?
The chocolate lava cake, the little soaps in the bathroom.
Le coulant, les petits savons.
And I'm sorry, but you're wearing more perfume than lam.
Et tu es encore plus parfumé que moi.
That's Unbreakable by Khloe and Lamar.
C‘est le parfum Unbreakable de Khloe and Lamar.
And for your information, it's unisex.
C‘est une fragrance unisexe.
Fill in the blank: "I love the nightlife...."
Complète la chanson : "I love the nightlife.…"
-I like to boogie. -Got you.
- "I like to boogie". - Ah !
With women. I like to boogie with women.
Avec des femmes. J'aime le boogie avec des femmes.
That's disappointing. You were exactly the kind of phony-baloney husband...
Quel dommage. Tu étais vraiment le mari bidon parfait
...l was looking for.
que je recherchais.
Thank you.
Merci.
And once again, my baloney likes girls.
Mon bidon aime les filles, je le rappelle.
Wait, wait. You don't wanna put a bite of that in your mouth...
Attends, ne goûte pas ça
...without trying my homemade Chantilly cream.
sans ma chantilly faite maison.
Yeah, okay, that time I heard it.
OK, je vois.
Oh, dear.
Mon Dieu.
Two suns and no sunscreen.
Deux soleils et pas d‘écran total.
Hello again, Sheldon.
On se retrouve, Sheldon,
What is it now, Tiny Spock?
Quoi encore, petit Spock ?
lam very disappointed in you.
Vous me décevez.
You broke your toy and switched it with Leonard's.
Vous avez échangé votre jouet cassé.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Honte sur vous.
You're the one who told me to play with it.
Vous m'avez dit de jouer.
If I told you to jump 017' the bridge of the Enterprise, would you do it?
Et si je vous disais de sauter du pont de [Enterprise ?
If I got on the bridge of the Enterprise, I would never ever leave.
Si j‘étais sur le pont de l'Enterprise,
Trust me, it gets old after a while.
On se lasse de tout, croyez-moi.
You must right your wrong, Sheldon.
Corrigez votre méfait.
Why? I got away with it.
Pourquoi ? Je ne risque rien.
Leonard has his toy, and he's never going to open it.
Leonard n‘ouvrirajamais sa boîte.
So he won't know it's broken. And I have a toy that isn't broken.
Il ignorera qu'il est cassé, etj'ai un jouet intact.
Everybody's happy.
Tout le monde est content.
Well, lam unhappy.
Pas moi.
I thought where you come from they don't have emotions.
La d'où vous venez, les émotions n'existent pas.
I come from a factory in Taiwan.
Je viens d‘une usine de Taiwan.
Now, do the right thing.
Faites ce qu‘il faut.
You know what you are?
Vous savez quoi ?
Well, you're a green-blooded buzzkill.
Vous êtes un rabat-joie au sang vert.
Perhaps it's time you beam on out of here.
Et si vous vous téléportiez ?
Fine. I will just use the Transporter.
Fort bien. ou est le téléporteur ?
Oh, right, you broke it.
Ah, j‘oubliais : vous l‘avez cassé.
Very well. Cooper to Enterprise, one to beam up.
Bien. Cooper a Enterprise, téléportation.
Energize.
Générateur !
-Ready for lunch? -Yeah, one sec. Ahh.
- On déjeune ? - Une seconde.
Oh, good. Ma would've killed me if she found out I broke my retainer.
Ma mère m'aurait tué si elle avait su que j‘avais cassé mon appareil.
Hey, uh, can I run something by you? It's about Lakshmi.
Je peux te demander un truc a propos de Lakshmi ?
Yeah, sure. How are things going?
Oui. Ça va?
We hit a couple of bumps.
Couci-couça.
She lives over in Manhattan Beach, so it takes like an hour to get there.
Elle vit à Manhattan Beach, à une heure de chez moi.
And she's a lesbian.
Et elle est lesbienne.
What do you mean, a lesbian?
Lesbienne ?
Well, you know whenever you and I would try to hit on women in bars...
Tu sais, quand des filles nous jettent
...they'd blow us off, then we'd tell each other they were gay?
et qu'on décide qu‘elles sont lesbiennes ?
It's like that.
C‘est pareil.
Except this time, it's true.
Sauf que la, c‘est vrai.
-Why did she even go out with you? -She was looking for a husband...
- Pourquoi te fréquenter, alors ? - Pour avoir un mari
...so she can appear to be straight.
et faire hétéro.
And, you know, it sounded crazy to me at first...
Et ça me paraissait dingue au début,
...but I'm actually thinking about doing it.
mais j'envisage de le faire.
Okay. Well, so the reason that might sound crazy is because it's crazy!
Si ça te parait dingue, c‘est parce que ça l'est.
Look, Howard, you're in a relationship.
Tu es en couple.
You know you have to make compromises.
Il faut faire des compromis.
Yes, but my compromises are about which bedspread to buy...
Les compromis, c‘est sur le choix de la couette,
...or whose turn it is to do the laundry, Bernadette's or my mom's.
sur qui fait la lessive, ma mére oula sienne.
It's a great deal. We both get our parents off our backs.
On serait libérés de nos parents.
I don't have to come home to an empty apartment.
Je ne serais pas seul le soir.
Plus, once I'm married, I can finally eat carbs again and let myself go.
Et une fois marié, plus de régime, je me laisse aller.
Why don't you tell your parents you wanna try to find someone else?
Pourquoi ne pas dire a tes parents d'en trouver une autre ?
You know, one who hasn't slept with more women than you.
Qui n'aurait pas eu plus de nanas que toi.
Because this one wants to marry me.
Parce que celle-là veut m'épouser.
I might never find another one who does.
Ce sera peut-être la seule.
You're thinking about marrying someone...
Tu vas épouser une femme
...you're never gonna have sex with?
avec qui tu ne coucheras jamais ?
I can't believe your attitude.
Je n'en reviens pas.
I thought you were in favor of gay people getting married.
Je te croyais pour le mariage des gays.
HOWARD: Yes, to other gay people.
Oui, avec d'autres gays.
RAJESH: Do you hear how homophobic you sound?
Tu es affreusement homophobe !
Oh, I don't want a broken toy.
Je ne veux pas un jouet cassé.
Nothing.
Rien.
-What? -Nothing. I said nothing.
- Quoi ? - Rien,je n'ai rien dit.
-That was weird. -Really? I don't even notice anymore.
- C‘était bizarre. -Ah ? Je ne remarque même plus.
We told you, you don't. It's mint-in-box.
Ça doit rester emballé.
I don't know. I just think it's a waste.
C‘est du gâchis.
Just relax, I'm just looking at the box.
Du calme, je regarde.
You should look with your eyes and not your muscular Nebraska man-hands.
Regarde avec les yeux, pas avec tes mains d'hommasse du Nebraska.
What is your problem?
Quel est ton problème ?
My problem is that I don't want you to break Leonard's toy...
Je ne veux pas que tu casses son jouet,
...which you probably did by shaking it. She shook it, we all saw her.
ce que tu as sûrement fait. On t‘a tous vue le secouer.
Leonard, I bought you this because I wanted you to have fun with it.
Je t'ai acheté ça pour que tu t'amuses avec.
I didn't want it to sit in this box.
Ne le laisse pas dans sa boîte.
You know what? You're right.
Tu as raison.
I mean, it's from you. I'm never gonna sell it.
Je ne le revendrai jamais.
-l'm opening it. -Yes.
- Je l'ouvre. - Oui.
-lt's broken. -What?
- Il est cassé. - Quoi ?
Oh, nice job, man-hands.
Bravo, l‘hommasse.
I didn't break it.
Ce n‘est pas moi.
I guess Stuart sold it to me like this.
Stuart a dû me le vendre cassé.
Yes. Yes, he did.
C‘est sûr.
That is a perfectly satisfying and plausible explana--
C‘est une explication plausible et satisfaisante.
You know, let's all be mad at Stuart.
Détestons tous Stuart.
I paid a lot for this. Let's take it over there and show him.
Il va m‘entendre, je l'ai payé une fortune.
Absolutely.
Absolument.
Wait.
Attendez.
It was me.
C‘est moi.
I opened your toy...
J'ai ouvert ton jouet,
...discovered it was broken, and didn't tell you.
j'ai vu qu'il était cassé et n'ai rien dit.
-Why would you open mine? -I didn't. That was a lie.
- Pourquoi tu as ouvert mon jouet ? - J'ai menti.
I opened my own toy...
J'ai ouvert le mien,
...and it was already broken, so I switched them.
il était cassé, alors j'ai échangé les boites.
-Well, you should talk to Stuart. -I can't, because that was a lie.
- Parles-en a Stuart. - Non, carj'ai menti.
Yours was broken in an earthquake and that's a lie.
Le tien a été cassé par un séisme. C‘est faux.
What is the truth?
La Vérité, c‘est quoi ?
My Mr. Spock doll came to me in a dream and forced me to open it.
Ma figurine Spock m‘a forcé à ouvrir mon jouet.
And when the toy broke, I switched it for yours.
Je l'ai cassé et l'ai échangé avec le tien.
Later, he encouraged me to do the right thing and l defied him.
Spock m‘a poussé à bien agir etje l'ai défié.
And then I was attacked by a Gorn.
Puis un Corn m‘a attaqué.
-Okay, that I believe. -Mm.
Je veux bien te croire.
Leonard, Penny, I want you both to know...
Leonard, Penny, sachez
...that I regret my actions towards the two of you. That's a lie.
que je regrette mes actes. C‘est faux.
So is that one mine?
Le mien, c‘est celui-là ?
-Yes. -Well, hand it over so I can open it.
- Oui. - Donne, que je l'ouvre.
And, Leonard, even though I don't have one anymore...
Leonard, même si je n'en ai plus,
-...I hope you have fun playing with it. -That's a lie?
-j'espére que tu t‘amuseras. - Tu mens ?
-A big, fat whopper. -Yeah.
- Et comment. - Oui.
I hope it breaks.
J'espère qu'il va casser.
This is a treat. What brings you guys by?
Qu'est-ce qui vous amène ?
Raj, Howie told me what's going on with you and Lakshmi.
Raj, Howie m‘a expliqué, pour Lakshmi.
-You told her? -I told everybody.
- Tu lui as dit ? -Atout le monde.
We believe there's someone out there who'll love you for you.
Il y a quelqu‘un, quelque part, qui t‘aimera.
We kind of agreed to disagree on that one.
Je ne suis pas trop d‘accord.
But we both think you shouldn't marry this woman.
Mais on est d'accord sur ça : ne l'épouse pas.
So while I'm waiting for this mysterious perfect match...
Donc en attendant cette moitié parfaite,
...who may or may not exist, I'm supposed to just be alone?
qui n'existe peut-être pas, je dois rester seul ?
I think we found someone for you to cuddle with.
On t‘a trouvé quelqu'un a câliner.
[RAJESH GASPS]
Ca alors.
Aren't you the cutest little Yorkie ever?
Tu es le plus mignon de tous les Yorks !
-You got him for me? -Her.
- Il esta moi ? - Elie.
We thought you two would hit it off.
On s‘est dit que ça collerait.
I think we already have. Thank you guys so much.
Oui. Merci beaucoup.
Let's go see if you fit in my man-purse.
Est-ce que tu rentres dans mon sac pour homme ?
Metrosexual, my ass.
Métrosexuel, mon cul.
[English - us - an]
[French]